examfx.com 2016-06-26

# ExamFX | Privacy Policy

  * our commitment to privacy
  * the information we collect from our online customers
  * how we use the personal information that we collect
  * disclosure of your personal information
  * consent
  * cookies
  * choice/opt-out
  * will information I submit in connection with an online transaction be protected?
  * what other data security measures do we have in place?
  * our commitment to children's privacy
  * links to other sites
  * privacy policy updates
  * access

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

back to top

We will track use of the website by our visitors, but unless you sign in as a customer such tracking will be done anonymously. You are not required to provide us with any information in order to browse our website. On some pages, you can purchase courses, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages, includes, but is not limited to: 

  * Name
  * Address
  * E-Mail address
  * Phone number
  * Social Security Number
  * Credit/Debit Card Information

back to top

We use personal information you submit for the following purposes:

  * to provide the products and services you request
  * to process your orders
  * to provide follow-up information about pertinent products and services
  * to contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current products and services or of potential new products or services that may be offered 

We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties unless needed to properly respond to your message. 

back to top

We do not sell or exchange any personal information of our customers with any third parties. To comply with state-imposed recordkeeping regulations, we report student course completion information (name, address, NPN, etc.) electronically to the appropriate regulatory agencies and their third party administrators. However, we may release your personal information in the event we are compelled to do so by court order or other requirement of law, or if we, in good faith, believe such release is advisable or necessary. Additionally, it is possible that in the future we may sell our online business. In connection with such a sale, your personal information may be transferred to a third party. 

back to top

By providing information on our website you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of such personal information in the manner described in this privacy policy. You may withdraw your consent at any time by following the procedure described in the Choice/Opt-Out provision set forth below. 

back to top

From time to time, for your convenience, we might issue you a "cookie" during your visit to our website. A cookie is a small file that contains information (such as your login name on our site) and is stored by your computer's browser. We do not use cookies for any reason other than to provide convenience to our visitors and improve their online experience. 

back to top

We may send you catalogs or e-mails to inform you of new products, services and special offers. If you would prefer not to be contacted about such special offers, products or services, please notify us of such preference using any of the contact information set forth below. Please be aware that we will honor all opt-out requests, however, there may be a delay between your submission of such request and the actual removal of your name and contact information from our mailing lists as these are generated well in advance of our actual mailings. 

  * **Call us:** 800-586-2253

back to top

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption, the industry standard for secure online transactions, to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. 

back to top

As required by various state-imposed recordkeeping regulations, and to maintain in the event of audit our ability to produce future proof that you completed a given course, we must retain your information indefinitely. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Personally identifiable information is maintained in a secure database accessible only by authorized staff. 

back to top

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

back to top

Our website may contain links to third party websites operated by individuals or companies unrelated to us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party websites. These linked websites are for your convenience only and you access them at your own risk. We recommend that you review the privacy policies posted on such third party websites prior to utilizing them. 

back to top

Occasionally, we may update our privacy policy and information security procedures. If our privacy and/or information security procedures change at any time in the future, we will post the new changes on our website to notify you and provide you with the ability to opt-out in accordance with the Choice/Opt-Out provisions set forth above. 

back to top

Please feel free to contact us at any time with any questions or comments you may have or to edit your personal information. We can be reached by any of the means of contact included in the **choice/opt-out** provision set forth above. 

back to top
